textgod.com 2019-07-19

# Privacy Policy

We consider the privacy of our visitors important and treat all personal information provided as confidential. All data is processed in accordance with the Data Protection Act.

We do this by, among other things:

Clearly state the purposes for which we process personal data.

Limit the collection of data to the data necessary for the intended purpose.

First ask permission in case it is required.

Not to pass on data to third parties, unless absolutely necessary, as explained in this statement.

Once we share data, make arrangements with these third parties that data will not be used for purposes other than those intended.

Protect and safeguard data.

Enabling you to view, correct or delete your own data.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, want to view information, changes about deletion, please contact us: Patrick@attractiongym.nl

(Lifestyle Ventures, Afroditekade 28b, 1076DP Amsterdam).

## Purposes

We process personal data for various reasons, each time processing only the data that is necessary for the purpose.

It concerns the following purposes:

Purchasing products and courses. These are the data needed to keep a correct customer administration and to be able to provide you with the relevant product or service.

Marketing purposes to keep you informed about products and offers.

Market research and analysis. Optimizing our website, products and services.

The fulfilment of statutory obligations and the obligation to keep records.

When you submit information on our website, for example via a form, this information is kept as long as it is necessary for the nature of the specific form.

We will only use your personal data if you give us permission to do so:

Data will only be shared with third parties if you explicitly give your consent. Unless we are legally obliged to do so, or it is necessary for the processing of an order.

## Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track how users use our website and how we can optimize our website. Personal data is completely anonymous and cannot be traced back to an individual or IP address. The data is kept on Google’s servers.

## PayPro

As a payment service we use PayPro. When you buy a product from us, the data is stored with PayPro.

## Mollie

For our coaching services we use Mollie as a payment service.

## Newsletter & Email

It is possible to subscribe to our newsletter, in which we regularly send you tips by e-mail and keep you informed of special offers.  

We use Active Campaign and Aweber to keep track of email addresses and first names and to send emails.

You will only receive this newsletter if you give your explicit permission to do so. And you can unsubscribe at any time via the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the emails.

## Facebook & Youtube

On this site there are several buttons for sharing or licking our Facebook and Youtube channels. This code is placed by means of a code that these parties provide themselves.

In addition, when you sign up for our newsletter on Facebook, you can occasionally receive targeted advertisements about our offers.

## Cookies

We use cookies. A cookie is a small and simple file that is automatically stored on your hard disk in a dedicated folder of your browser.

We use the following cookies:

Functional cookies. These are cookies that are simply necessary for the website to function properly. For example, to keep track of the fact that you have already seen the cookie popup.

Google Analytics. We use this to analyse general use of our website and to improve the website.

OptinMonster. This places a cookie as soon as you have seen a certain popup, so that it does not appear again.

## Access to and correction of data

If you have a relationship with us in any way, you have the right to access, modify and delete your data. The latter only if we are not legally obliged to retain your data.

Please contact us via patrick@attractiongym.nl

## Security

We take your privacy seriously and do everything we can to ensure that all your data is as secure as possible. For example, every page where you leave your data has an encrypted HTTPS connection, and we include security in all agreements with our suppliers.
